gearvita.com 2019-07-06

# Privacy Policy | GearVita

If we make changes to this Privacy Policy, we will post an updated version on our website. Please review this policy from time to time. If you have any questions relating to the Privacy Policy or general Terms & Conditions, please contact us at [service@gearvita.com](mailto:cs@gearvita.com?subject=Service%20Request%20from)

#### Introduction

This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, disclose and safeguard your personal information. The security of your personal information is of utmost importance, so we are committed to maintaining the confidentiality of all personal information you have provided to us and we take all reasonable precautions to protect your personal information from unauthorized use. We will also take efforts to comply with the applicable laws under which we process the information collected from you. By using and accessing this website, you accept the practices described under this policy.

#### Collection of Personal Information

We collect information about you when you visit our website and use our services. When you provide us with information, you consent to the transfer and storage of information on our servers.

#### Use and Disclosure of Personal Information

Personal information that we collect from you will be used and disclosed only to provide products and services to you, or otherwise to carry out our business.

Types of personal information we may use and disclose include:• Internally to provide a service to you• Communicating with you• Legal Purposes

There may be some circumstances where will be legally required to share personal information.• Externally

We may share your information with third parties we engage with to perform services on our behalf. For example sharing logistics information: fulfilling and delivering packages, receiving packages, enabling access to affiliated business websites etc. However, we will not sell or loan your information to third parties unless we ask for your permission upfront.• Data Retention

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active with us or as required to provide services to you. We will also retain data in compliance with our legal obligations.

We will ask for your consent before releasing information about you to third parties outside those stated above.

#### Security and Protection of your personal information

Our website is secured and encrypted using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. Our servers are located in the United States of America (USA), and we also take measures to protect your personal information in our facilities and protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use. While we use industry standard software to safeguard your personal information, we cannot guarantee complete security of your personal information. We also protect your personal information through the use of password controls that we ask you to keep confidential. We will never ask you for your password, and you may change it at anytime under “My Account”.

#### Children and Privacy

Our websites do not target and are not intended to attract children under the age of 18. We do not knowingly solicit personal information from children under the age of 18 or send them requests for personal information.

#### Third Party Sites

Our website contains links to other websites operated by other companies. We do not share your personal information with those websites (unless we have asked for your permission as stated above) and are not responsible for their privacy practices.

We encourage you to check the applicable privacy policy of the third party website to determine how they will handle any information they collect from you.

#### Business Transitions

In the event that we go through a business transition, such as a merger or acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your personal information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via prominent notice on our website for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.
